Dr Elena Hill-Artamonova

24 Chester street, Chester, Saltney, CH4 8BJ, 07944938651 Email: elena.hillartamonova92@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Diligent and motivated researcher with a proven record of generating and building relationships, researching projects, designing and implementing questionnaires for variety of purposes. Meticulously investigating and researching diverse avenues to achieve desired outcomes. Skilled in a cross-cultural and behavioural research, demonstrating exceptional communication skills, making critical decisions during challenges, highly efficient in lead generation both during work experiences and education. Self-motivated in all areas of research and analysis, obtaining expectation-exceeding results through publishing articles, blog posts, presentations and conference attendance. Highly specialised in statistical analysis including but not limited to CFA, SEM and invariance analysis. Highly skilled and trained in obtaining, analysing and presenting vast amount of data.

WORK HISTORY

Senior Research Manager | 11/2021 - current - Talent Works International Consulting

- Created and led number of research projects into understating recruitment behaviour, as well as, proprietary research for women in technology industry
- Engaged with international clients on research into Brand and Insights
- Engaged with senior stakeholders and directors on issues of research and implementation of new quantitative/qualitative methods of analysis
- Created discussion guides for CEO's, senior stakeholders and employees
- Led focus groups online and face-to-face
- Designed questionnaires using online survey platforms i.e. Qualtrics and PollFish
- Analysed large amount of qualitative data using AtlasTI
- Programmed in R
- Created Knowledge hub to share skills between departments

Senior Research Officer | 03/2021 - 11-2021 - Office for National Statistics

- Led Student Insights into Covid pandemic and NHS Test and Trace surveys
- Created questionnaires
- Engaged with stakeholder and senior management
- Engaged with media and press

- Analysed large scale datasets
- Coded in SPSS and R Programming
- Led a team of research officers in fast paced environment

RESEARCH ASSISTANT | 02/2019 - Current Applied Research Team, Manchester Metropolitan University - Manchester

- Collected qualitative and quantitative data using varied techniques including survey/ questionnaires and interviews, as well as, write up methodology sections of papers for publication.
- Inspired and engaged students using interesting examples, as well as, devoted extra time after lectures for Q&A meetings.
- Optimised development and subject enthusiasm.
- Created teaching programmes (lectures and presentations) to meet necessary subject requirements and produce well-equipped, well-educated students.
- Demonstrated expertise in psychology, statistics and research methods and offered engaging, insightful lectures and seminars.
- Implemented diverse instructional approaches to engage students and promote deeper understanding of material.
- Developed and updated source syllabi to comply with changing course plans.
- Responsible for creating, designing and quality assurance of the surveys Researched and updated all required materials needed for university and department.
- Managing student classes up to 200 students.
- Creating extra tutoring classes out of my own expense to help student master statistical
- Inspired and engaged students using interesting examples and extra supporting to optimise development and subject enthusiasm.
- Prepared and implemented lesson plans covering required course topics.

ASSOCIATE LECTURER | 01/2018 – 12/2019 Manchester Metropolitan University

- Led interesting and diverse group activities to engage students in course material.
- Worked with administrators on behavioural issues to support needs of all students.
- Used different instructional techniques to obtain and retain student interest in subject matter.

• Managed up to 200 student classes each semester for both undergraduate and graduate-level students.

CHECK IN AND CHAT VOLUNTEER | 03/2020 - 03/2022, Mersey Care NHS trust - Liverpool

- Collaborated with social services, referral sources, and other professionals, including Mersey Care and NHS to meet patient needs.
- Maintained constant contact with service users, as well as, used clinical and behavioural knowledge to maintain safety during crisis moments.
- Used clinical and behavioural knowledge to maintain safety during crisis moments.
- Researched, trained and obtained psychological first aid certificate to help service users to the best of my abilities.

MOBILITY AIDS VOLUNTEER | 03/2018 - 03/2020 British Red Cross - Shrewsbury Responsible for providing access to wheelchair for anyone in need

VOLUNTEER | 05/2017 – 02/2019

Animal Welfare Party - London

Responsible for creating spreadsheets through Microsoft software, as well as, communication with potential suppliers.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT DATA ANALYST $\mid 09/2016 - 09/2018$ Prejudice Lab at Goldsmith University - London

Responsible for data analysis through SPSS and EXLSTAT. As well as, research for publications.

DEPUTY ASSISTANT OF THE MP \mid 09/2013 - 09/2016 Parliament of Russian Federation - Moscow

Helped to write and research speeches, organise files, research into public policies and participate in presentations and conferences.

CORPORATE RISK AND DUE DILIGENCE | 02/2016 - 08/2016 Interfax - London

Was responsible for sales of highly effective anti-corruption software, client relationships and lead generations.

BEAUTY CONSULTANT | 02/2015 - 10/2015 **Selfridges - Manchester** Was responsible for direct sales of the products in a competitive environment, as well as, building relationships to establish strong client base.

INTERN | 01/2015 - 09/2015

North West Employers - Manchester

Was responsible for research into public policies and communication with government organisations.

ONLINE BASED JOURNALIST AND PHOTOGRAPHER | 11/2013 - 10/2014 InterFax media organisation - Moscow

Was responsible for content creation, photographs and research for articles.

SKILLS

- SPSS/R software
- Data collection and analysis
- Data management
- Communication and presentation
- Microsoft Office
- Survey design, implementation and quality assurance
- Questionnaire programming and testing
- Data processing
- Qualitative and Quantitative research
- Project management
- Critical thinking, conflict resolution and stakeholder engagement

EDUCATION

Manchester Metropolitan University - Manchester, Ph.D.

Psychology, March 2022

Personality psychology with emphasis on prejudice, aggression, narcissism, psychopathy, Big Five personality factors, data analysis via SPSS, SAS and M-Plus, as well as, survey design and implementation.

Goldsmiths, University of London - London, Master of Science

Social Psychology, 12/2017

Areas of focus: Social relations, Forensic Psychology, Addictive Behaviour, Violence, Conflict, Intergroup Perspective, Narcissism, Interpersonal Self, organisational psychology, survey design and implementation.

University of Manchester - Manchester, United Kingdom | Master of Arts

Governance and Public Policy, 12/2015

Areas of focus: governance and welfare state, globalisation, public policy, rhetorics, relationship between business and government.

University of Wales Trinity St. David - Lampeter, Ceredigion, United Kingdom | Bachelor of Arts

Anthropology, 2014

Areas of study included: Social Anthropology, Archaeology and Religious Study.

St.Petersburg University of State Fire Service of The Ministry of the Russian Federation - St. Petersburg, Russia | Bachelor of Science

Psychology, 2014

Areas of study included: Psychology, Mathematics, English, Counselling training.

City Of London Freemen's School - Ashtead, Surrey, United Kingdom | A-Levels

Business Studies, Psychology, Government and Politics, 2011 Business studies; Psychology; Government and Politics.

DIPLOMAS AND CERTIFICATIONS

Advanced Counselling Diploma Level 4 - April 2021.

Market Research certificate - December 2021.

Cognitive Behavioural Training diploma level 3 - Expected June 2022.

Life coaching diploma level 4 - Expected June 2022.

LANGUAGES

Russian - fluent; English - fluent; French-intermediate; Spanish - intermediate.